onewed.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy for OneWed.com

## Privacy Policy

Posted July 9th 2008

OneWed.com’s Privacy Policy will help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using OneWed.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "OneWed.com" or "Site") By using or accessing OneWed.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This privacy statement covers the site www.onewed.com and its directly associated domains. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us by mail at OneWed.com Privacy Officer, OneWed Inc. 1043 St Patrick Street, Victoria, BC, Canada V8S 4Y2.

#### Information Collected By Us

When you visit the Site you provide us with two types of information: personal information you choose to disclose and Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Site.You may provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, and any other personal or preference information.

When you visit and enter the Site, we collect your browser type and IP address. We also store information from your browser using "cookies," pieces of data stored on your computer that is tied to information about the user. For example, we may use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you return. You can manage use of cookies through your browser settings.

When you use the Site, you may set up your personal profile, send messages, search for information, form groups, set up events, and transmit information. We collect this information so that we can provide you service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that you can find it again. When you update information, we may keep the prior version for a period of time.

You post user content on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users or visitors who may see your information. We cannot guarantee that content you post will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. You understand and acknowledge that, copies of removed content may remain viewable in cached/archived pages or if stored by others.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on OneWed.com is a violation of the OneWed.com Terms of Service and should be reported to us. If you choose to use our Service to tell someone about the Site, such as to invite them to join or view your wedding planning pages, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We store this information to send this one-time invitation, and to track the success of our referral program. We may, from time to time, email your guests in response to communication or action on the site or to offer products or services we think may be of interest.

By using the Site, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and elsewhere.

#### Children Under 13

The Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to sign up. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to sign up for OneWed.com or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on OneWed.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [http://support.onewed.com](http://support.onewed.com/).

#### Children Between 13 and 18

OneWed.com’s Terms of Use do not permit registration by, use of or access to the Site other than as a visitor, by anyone under 18 without permission of a parent or legal guardian. We recommend that minors aged 13 to 18 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet, including before sending any information to us or anyone else using the Site or Service.

#### Use of Information

When you sign up with OneWed.com, you submit certain information to the Site. Your information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed so that you can connect with people. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by or through OneWed.com that we think you may find valuable. Your information is used by OneWed.com primarily to be presented to others permitted to view that information. In some cases, other Site users (for example, members of your wedding party) may be able to supplement your profile.

Profile information you submit to OneWed.com will be available to users and visitors of OneWed.com. Your Site user name and other information will be available to users and visitors of the Site, and limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends and family can find your wedding pages. All content posted in the site’s community areas is public, including user-created wedding pages and content added to those pages. Our forms for checking the availability of a vendor for a certain date, or to request a quote from a vendor, are forwarded only to the selected vendor. Where you submit information to the Site, you generally cannot remove such communications.

OneWed.com may send you announcements from time to time including newsletters and information on new OneWed features. For instance, if someone sends you a message, if someone posts on a forum in response to you, or if there is a bridal show coming to your area, you may receive an email alerting you. For purposes of connecting you to the vendors you need, the Company may disclose your information to our affiliated vendors of wedding-related goods and services or otherwise. We may also disclose general, non-identifying information about you to third parties for purposes such as aggregating users’ and visitors’ Site behavior and preferences, and personalizing advertisements and promotions that support OneWed.com.

#### Sharing Information

OneWed.com is about sharing information with you, and with your friends, family, and people involved with your wedding, which may include actual or potential vendors. From time to time, OneWed does share names and email addresses and demographic information with pre-screened third-party organizations with related products and services that may be of interest to you. You may choose to remove yourself from these mailing lists by contacting support@onewed.com. We may provide information to service providers with which we partner to bring you services. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host or co-host our computer servers, or to send out emails. Where third parties assist with the processing of personal information, we take reasonable steps to limit the use of that information.

We may be required to disclose user information in response to legal requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or as required by law or regulation, but we do not disclose information without a belief that such a request meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

We may offer products or services jointly with other companies. You will be able to tell when another company is involved, and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your interest in such products or services.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Company changes, your information may be transferred to the new owner. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

#### Advertising

Advertisements that appear on the Site are sometimes delivered to our users by third party advertisers. Those third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens. Such advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" to track the effectiveness of their ads and/or to customize ad content. This allows the advertisers to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement, to collect information about where your computer or browser saw their advertisements, and to determine which advertisements are clicked. OneWed.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on OneWed.com unless you choose to share it with them. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by OneWed.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. OneWed.com contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. Please be aware when you leave the Site to read the privacy statements of each site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by OneWed.com.

#### Security

OneWed.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. If you enter information such as a credit card number or your password, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Email and instant messaging are not regarded as secure media, so please do not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any security questions, please contact us by mail at OneWed.com Privacy Officer, OneWed Inc. 1043 St Patrick Street, Victoria, BC, Canada V8S 4Y2.

#### Policies, Revisions, Notices

Your use of the Site, including any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all dispute resolution provisions therein, including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us by mail at OneWed.com Privacy Officer, OneWed Inc. 1043 St Patrick Street, Victoria, BC, Canada V8S 4Y2.
